https://www.suusi.org/privacy-policy-2-2/

By Age
Youth (0-10)
Important Information
Middlers (11-13)
Coming of Age Program For 13 Year-Olds
Teens (14-17)
Guidelines for Parents & Guardians of Teens
Young Adults (18-25)
Medians (Over 21)
Adults (21+)
Late Night Food & Drink
Come this Summer!
Housing & Dining
Take a SUUSI Tour!
By Age
Youth (0-10)
Important Information
Middlers (11-13)
Coming of Age Program For 13 Year-Olds
Teens (14-17)
Guidelines for Parents & Guardians of Teens
Young Adults (18-25)
Medians (Over 21)
Adults (21+)
Late Night Food & Drink
Come this Summer!
Housing & Dining
Take a SUUSI Tour!
Effective Date: 2/22/2018
SUUSI is the Southeast Unitarian Universalist Summer Institute, inc., a privately owned, non profit, IRS recognized 501(c)(3) corporation registered in the state of Florida.
SUUSI has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to our participant’s privacy. We do not give, sell, rent, share, show or trade any personally identifiable information regarding our particpants’ to any third party.
Please note that this privacy policy ONLY applies to the SUUSI.ORG website. Solis, the SUUSI registration web application, has its own privacy policy and terms of use.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
From time to time, we may make changes to this privacy statement, so please review it frequently. Whenever we make a change, we will post or otherwise make available the revised privacy statement. We will endeavor to post the changes before they become effective. The effective date of the most recent version of this privacy statement will appear at the top of the statement.
This privacy statement applies to any information we collect. If we make any material changes to this privacy statement we will notify you here, by email or by means of a notice on our home page.
Information Automatically Collected through Visits to the Site
You can access our web site and browse our site without disclosing your personal data.
Our site automatically logs each visit information through web server logging, WordPress site statistics, and Google Analytics. These tools capture information such as current IP address, general location and demographic information (if you provided it to Google), pages visited and pathways, pages shared on social media (but not specific individuals or accounts), search terms and results, and how you found us (referring links, a bookmark or a search engine).
his information is aggregated and not usually able to be personally identified. The information is only available to SUUSI web host Site Ground and SUUSI communication staff, and is used for site security and performance tracking, as well as learning how best to provide information to our users. For more information on how this information is used, please contact communications@suusi.org.
Terms of Use for Contributed Content
Voluntary Contributions of Content and Images to SUUSI
Our website enables you to communicate with SUUSI Staff and other visitors via comments or to provide information to SUUSI staff (contact us, Submit NUUS, Submit Website content) for the purpose of communication with staff and/or publication on the website or SUUSI NUUS (print and web). In order to submit this information, you will need to provide your name and an email address.
Your Agreements on Contributed Content
When you share this information with SUUSI, you are explicitly asking SUUSI staff or designates to share this information (including images and files) either with other staff or publicly unless otherwise stated.
You are also stating that you have the appropriate copyright/IP ownership over any content provided, and you have obtained informed consent for photographs or personal information provided.
You also agree to not share information or images that violates SUUSI’s Anti-Harassment Policies, an
It is SUUSI policy to explicitly confirm consent for photographs and information of children under the age of 18.
While our staff will try to protect sensitive information provided to us, this website is not the appropriate venue for such information. In a case of needing to share sensitive information, we recommend you contact one of the members of the SUUSI core staff and request a call.
Disclosure and visitor choice
We do not disclose your personal data to our affiliates or other organizations.
Confidentiality and security
A secure transmission method is always used when sending us the following types of personal data:
primary personal data (such as name and contact details)
other personal and profiling data (such as physical description, leisure activities)
identifiers (such as credit card details, web site password)
specific personal data (such as racial or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, medical data)
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from:
unauthorized access
improper use or disclosure
unauthorized modification
unlawful destruction or accidental loss
All our volunteers and data processors who have access to and are associated with the processing of personal data are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data. We insure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation.
Access to the personal data we may hold about you
You can ask us, by sending an email (privacy@suusi.org) whether we are keeping personal data about you. Upon request, which you can indicate by sending an e-mail (privacy@suusi.org), we will provide you with a readable copy of the personal data which we keep about you, although we may before require proof of your identity. We will provide the information without any charge.
We allow you to challenge the data that we hold about you and, where appropriate, you may have the data erased, rectified or amended.
PRIVACY SUPPORT
If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact:
SUUSI Board of Directors
1704 Bearhollow Rd., Greensboro, NC 27410
540-585-4336privacy@suusi.org
SUUSI 2021 startsJuly 18, 20217 months to go.A Day in the Life at SUUSI
Test Your SUUSI Lingo!Concert HourClick on the word to see if you got it right or click here to see the full glossary!
SOLIS is our online registration system.
